<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>02/16 Partner Newsletter.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Stencil in Action, New Partner Locator, and Bigcommerce at Fashion Week</subject>
    <textOnly>Preview text
Headline Copy
Exclusive offers, expanded label printing and more
Stencil in action  

In addition to a new theme marketplace, Bigcommerce recently launched its new theme development framework, Stencil, to select merchant stores. The response has been positive as merchants explore the new themes.
What’s next? The product teams at Bigcommerce are hard at work on a Stencil version release that will enable all partners that are working with Stencil to automatically upload custom themes.  This functionality will be available starting in June 2016.  If you are working on a custom theme for a merchant and plan for the store to launch before June 2016, please contact your account manager.  
For more information, you can access technical documentation and apply for early access to the Stencil CLI here &lt;[[http://stencil.bigcommerce.com/]]&gt;.  If you have an existing client interested in upgrading, please register them here &lt;[[https://www.bigcommerce.com/new-themes/]]&gt;.
Bigcommerce in the news

Luxury fashion designer LaQuan Smith is launching his redesigned Bigcommerce store alongside his new collection at Fashion Week. The brand aims to sell the collection immediately at the fashion show, creating a seamless purchase experience from the runway to consumers’ closets. Read more on Elle.com &lt;[[http://www.elle.com/fashion/a33842/laquan-smith-designer-fall-2016/]]&gt;.
Don’t miss In the Black magazine’s February issue, which features an executive profile &lt;[[http://intheblack.com/articles/2016/02/01/bigcommerce-preparing-a-company-for-public-listing]]&gt; on Bigcommerce CEO, Brent Bellm.
Partner Marketplace coming soon

Bigcommerce just made it easier than ever for merchants to find the right design and solution partner.  In March, Bigcommerce will launch a new merchant-facing, faceted search tool on Bigcommerce.com designed to help clients find the right partner for their design and solution needs. This new and improved search functionality will replace the current Bigcommerce Experts page &lt;[[https://www.bigcommerce.com/experts/]]&gt;.  Within the next few weeks, you’ll receive more information on how to submit your company’s information for inclusion in this lead-generation tool.

Questions about changes to Bigcommerce pricing

In January, Bigcommerce communicated updates to pricing plans to all clients, even those who were not affected. If you, or your clients, have any questions about these changes, check out the pricing FAQ &lt;[[http://partners.bigcommerce.com/English/Solutions/home.aspx]]&gt; on the partner portal.  In addition, your channel account manager is available to walk you through the new pricing model.
Product updates

ShipperHQ now available
Bigcommerce and ShipperHQ have teamed up to provide your merchants with highly flexible shipping management. To celebrate the Bigcommerce ShipperHQ integration, the app is now available with a 30-day free trial.
Install the app now from the Bigcommerce Control Panel (under Settings &gt; Shipping) or via the Bigcommerce Marketplace &lt;[[https://www.bigcommerce.com/apps/shipperhq/]]&gt;. 
Connect Bigcommerce with Xero
Don’t forget — Xero is now offering Bigcommerce merchants 30% off the first 6 months &lt;[[http://info.bigcommerce.com/e1t/c/*W715Qh53_4_kGW1Pllpp14BzbR0/*W4Nc3m450k20dW7SVDvw8xpNm40/5/f18dQhb0Smj18YXN5qW3rDyNF7PKkCqW11PvJW65jMbvW1pHdXW39SCJnW2K4V9Y8--HBkW8ZLtx78Vnr0LW4dQ25n7Lk5TzW3VNQVd4Bs6cnW4yx_7c5gYD-5W12tL7f5B4_wWW1tbf355F_2JdW3YJ0WC5W7sw9W22WLyB6HBHnDW6qG73421_n-FW6wBzg_22RyTCW1bK39W80vz2ZW89GBQx1xs02cW5_fmD67H19yXW7m-BrH7lTWPVW6KMcS31X46McW7N_l4S7DRjs5W708zxH6WkL3JW6tJNGJ77cC5QW6Pzq4t2dFfj0W1TVh5N22RR9BW1lCWzy1TmGKxW7XPTd87x5sJJW1ybZ3H1fPtxxW4KfDzc1jNNC_W37P0d415hnZlW2-9yN051m_7mW4rJ4xt25NHxTW6wFdv-2bHX5TW1nCrbg1RCMkZW62nPmF2fPyjyW3y9jS_1sFCDpW5vXLn85zSKQyN8T7fG7cYWZCVcSt5p2p2Vj5102]]&gt; on all new account sign ups for a limited time!  
Merchants can integrate their store with Xero’s accounting software to automatically sync their product, sales, customer, tax, payment and shipping data. Check out the new features recently added: inventory tracking and enhanced tax code mapping.
Upcoming events

February Bigcommerce Town Hall
Join this monthly conversation in which Bigcommerce Chief Executive Officer, Brent Bellm, and Chief Product Officer, Tim Schulz, provide a detailed look at recent platform enhancements and what’s coming up next.
When: Tuesday, February 23, 2016 2:00- 3:00pm CST
What: A discussion of Bigcommerce news and a look at upcoming product enhancements, followed by live Q&amp;A.
Who: CEO Brent Bellm and CPO Tim Schulz
Reserve your spot &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/5863786043245097730]]&gt;. 
We’ll hold a live Q&amp;A session during the Town Hall, but you can also submit questions in advance by commenting in our community forum &lt;[[http://forum.bigcommerce.com/f67/february-town-hall-coming-soon--27865/]]&gt;. 
Bigcommerce Lounge during SXSW Interactive
If you will be in Austin next month for SXSW, take a break during Interactive and stop by the Bigcommerce Lounge in our downtown office location. You can relax in our wi-fi enabled lounge, charge your devices, enjoy snacks and coffee served by local Austin favorite Houndstooth, network with your peers, and enjoy product previews and demos from the Bigcommerce team.
When: Monday, March 14, 2016 12:00- 5:00pm CST
What: A relaxing lounge for you to recharge in during SXSW Interactive. 
Where: Bigcommerce&apos;s Downtown Office &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps/place/Brazos+Place/@30.269794,-97.7409414,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x3f87410ac4f5831c]]&gt; — 800 Brazos St # 310 Austin, TX 78701
Who: The Bigcommerce Partner Team 
Missed a webinar? These replays are now available.
Understanding the Difference Between Sales and Use Taxes &lt;[[http://info.bigcommerce.com/avalara-webinar-on-demand]]&gt;
Avalara&apos;s tax technology expert explains the world of sales and use tax regulation.
Leveraging Bigcommerce and Skubana to Sell More On and Off Amazon &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LJiquaMVjak]]&gt;
Executive panel of ecommerce experts discuss key resolutions and success strategies needed to grow your business in 2016.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
